{
    "subject": "resource/Erich_Mende",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Mende",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Erich Mende is Mende.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9841236472129822,
            "question": "What is the surname of Erich Mende?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8927760720252991,
            "question": "Can you find any information about someone named Erich Mende?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8235204815864563,
            "question": "What other names might Erich Mende go by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7411152720451355,
            "question": "Is 'Mende' a common surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.685883104801178,
            "question": "Are there any famous people with the surname 'Mende'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6516861915588379,
            "question": "Can you find any historical figures with the surname 'Mende'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6459124088287354,
            "question": "What are some potential meanings or origins of the surname 'Mende'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.618970513343811,
            "question": "Are there any organizations or places named after the surname 'Mende'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5917679667472839,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the surname 'Mende' and genetics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5209826231002808,
            "question": "How common is the surname 'Mende' in different countries?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Erich Mende is Mende.",
            "html": "dbpedia_642_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between the surname 'Mende' and genetics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_642_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any organizations or places named after the surname 'Mende'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_642_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential meanings or origins of the surname 'Mende'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_642_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_642_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that the surname of Erich Mende is indeed \"Mende\", as mentioned in multiple files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_642/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt, 40.txt, and 81.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response indicates that the information provided in the documents supports the statement that the surname of Erich Mende is Mende."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}